let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which of the following is a vector quantity?",
        answer: "D. Force",
        options: [
            "A. Temperature",
            "B. Mass",
            "C. Distance",
            "D. Force"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "The energy an object possessess due to its motion is called:",
        answer: "B. Kinetic energy",
        options: [
            "A. Potential energy",
            "B. Kinetic energy",
            "C. Elasic energy",
            "D. Mechanical energy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "If a force of 10 N is applied to an object for 5 seconds, what is the impluse of force?",
        answer: "B. 50 N s ",
        options: [
            "A. 2 N s",
            "B. 50 N s ",
            "C. 2 N ",
            "D. 50 N"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "The Linear momentum of an object is defined as:",
        answer: "B. Mass*Velocity ",
        options: [
            "A. Mass*Acceleration ",
            "B. Mass*Velocity ",
            "C. Acceleration*Velocity ",
            "D. Mass/Volume"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "The reciprocal of resistance is known as:",
        answer: "B.Conductance",
        options: [
            "A. Impedance ",
            "B. Conductance ",
            "C. Capacitance ",
            "D. Susceptance "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which temperature scale is an absolute temperature scale?",
        answer: "C.Kelvin",
        options: [
            "A.Celsius ",
            "B.Fahrenheit ",
            "C.Kelvin",
            "D.Rankine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The SI unit of amplitude is:",
        answer: "C.Meter",
        options: [
            "A.Hertz ",
            "B.Watt",
            "C.Meter ",
            "D.Decibel "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "The chemical formula of hydrochloric acid is_________.",
        answer: "A. HCl",
        options: [
            "A. HCl",
            "B. H2SO4",
            "C. HNO3",
            "D. CH3COOH"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of the following is an example of strong base?",
        answer: "D. NaOH ",
        options: [
            "A. NH4OH",
            "B.Ca(OH)2",
            "C. Both A and B ",
            "D. NaOH "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which of the following is an example of weak acid?",
        answer: "B. Acetic acid",
        options: [
            "A.Hydrochrolic acid ",
            "B.Acetic acid",
            "C.Sulphuric acid",
            "D.Nitric acid "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Which gas is produced by the reaction of acid with metal?",
        answer: "A. Hydrogen",
        options: [
            "A.Hydrogen ",
            "B.Oxygen",
            "C.Carbon dioxide ",
            "D.Nitrogen "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Gardens are example of ",
        answer: " B. Artificial ecosystem",
        options: [
            "A. Natural ecosystem",
            "B. Artificial ecosystem",
            "C. Ecology",
            "D. Environment"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Whice of the following is a non-renewable energy resource?",
        answer: "D. Coal ",
        options: [
            "A. Solar",
            "B. Methane",
            "C. Hydroelectric",
            "D. Coal"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "What is the smallest unit of information?",
        answer: "B. Bit ",
        options: [
            "A. Byte",
            "B. Bit",
            "C. MB",
            "D. GB"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "What is the default extension of a microsoft excel file?",
        answer: "C. xlsx ",
        options: [
            "A. msxcl",
            "B. xcl",
            "C. xlsx",
            "D. xlsm"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "Rima is a good dancer. The underlined word “good” in the sentence given is________.",
        answer: "B. an adjective",
        options: [
            "A. a noun",
            "B. an adjective",
            "C. a verb",
            "D. an adverb"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "___________ you work hard, you will succeed in the university Examination.",
        answer: "D. If ",
        options: [
            "A. Though",
            "B. But",
            "C. Unless",
            "D. If"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "One of my friends __________ old.",
        answer: "B. is ",
        options: [
            "A. am",
            "B. is",
            "C. are",
            "D. has"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Choose the correct spelling.",
        answer: "B. Vacuum",
        options: [
            "A. Vaccum",
            "B. Vacuum",
            "C. Vacumm",
            "D. Veccum"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "Choose the correct spelling.",
        answer: "C. Entrepreneur",
        options: [
            "A. Enterpreneur",
            "B. Entreorenure",
            "C. Entrepreneur",
            "D. Enterprenure"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "Choose the correct sentence.",
        answer: "D.He is reading a book now.",
        options: [
            "A.He is reading a book yesterday. ",
            "B.He reads a book now.",
            "C.He read a book now.",
            "D.He is reading a book now."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "Choose the correct sentence.",
        answer: "A. I don’t use public transportdaily.",
        options: [
            "A. I don’t use public transportdaily.",
            "B. I didn’t use public transport daily.",
            "C. I not use public transport daily.",
            "D. I not using public transport daily."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "The person who transmit the message is called what?",
        answer: "B. Sender",
        options: [
            "A. Channel",
            "B. Sender",
            "C. Receiver",
            "D. Respondent"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "If the order of the matrix A is 4*3 orde of matrix B is 3*5 and the order of matri ABC is 4*2 then the order of matrix C is :",
        answer: "D. 5*2",
        options: [
            "A. 4*2",
            "B. 3*2",
            "C. 2*2",
            "D. 5*2"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "For square matrix A if 1/A=adjA then |A|= ?",
        answer: "A. 1",
        options: [
            "A. 1",
            "B. 0",
            "C. -1",
            "D. None of above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 26,
        question: "If vectors (m,3,5) and (m,m-1,-3) are perpendicular to each other then m=_____?",
        answer: "B. 0",
        options: [
            "A. 3",
            "B. 0",
            "C. 2",
            "D. 6"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 27,
        question: "Equation of line perpendicular to line 3x-2y+7=0 and passess through (3,2) is ___",
        answer: "B. 2x+3y-5=0",
        options: [
            "A. 3x+2y-11=0",
            "B. 2x+3y-5=0",
            "C. 2x+3y+12=0",
            "D. 2x+3y-12=0"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 28,
        question: "If x=a(1+sin0),y=a(1-cos0) then dy/dx =",
        answer: "D. sec 0",
        options: [
            "A. cot 0",
            "B. sin 0",
            "C. tan 0",
            "D. sec 0"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 29,
        question: "sin2A+sin8A/cos2A+cos8A =____",
        answer: "C. tan 5A",
        options: [
            "A. cot 5A",
            "B. tan 10A",
            "C. tan 5A",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 30,
        question: "If mean of 3,5,a,4,6 is 5 then a=___",
        answer: "C. 7",
        options: [
            "A. 5",
            "B. 6",
            "C. 7",
            "D. 8"
        ]
    }
];
